[Music]
you're not going to support me even
though you know I'm the best thing that
could ever happen to Israel I'm the
classiest holiest milk and honei
candidate you've got I'm like Moses only
less of a
loser 40 years to get out of the desert
come on I would have done it a week and
left the luxurious wall is is is is is
is is is is now I get it you're the
president and you think if you say isol
enough well start saying it that's not
how things catch on we heard it as Isis
the first time Isis is an easier word to
rhyme like Crisis the ISIS crisis we're
not having a national crysal like if you
come in front of a group of of uh
Republican black men and you're like so
what's up with them big dicks though
broad though a broad blanket statement
we accept it let that happen at the next
one man we would like
that please you're not you're really not
my con Happ the Coalition ever by the
way hey America Larry Wilmore here if
you like the nightly show on Comedy
Central like us on Facebook too just
don't poke me I do not like being poked
you can Candy Crush me